export const PROBLEM_OF_MONTH_2014 = [
  {
    month: "January",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1312q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1401a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Uwe Schafer", affiliation: "Dreieich, Germany" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "February",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1401q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1402a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Hamidbek Hajiyev", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Shatlyk Mamedov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, UK" },
      { name: "Uwe Schafer", affiliation: "Dreieich, Germany" },
      { name: "Hursant Kerimov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Myrat Chashemov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Alisher Ismailov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Osman Asil", affiliation: "Celal Bayar University, Manisa" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Onur Enginer", affiliation: "" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "Hakan Summakoğlu", affiliation: "Antakya, Hatay" },
      { name: "Dovran Nurgeldiyev", affiliation: "Turgut Özal Turkmen-Turk High School, Turkmenistan" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "March",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1402q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1403a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Jan Fricke", affiliation: "University of Siegen, Germany" },
      { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Lisesi" },
      { name: "Lim Chang Kiat", affiliation: "Malaysia" },
      { name: "Uwe Schafer", affiliation: "Dreieich, Germany" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "April",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1403q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1404a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Leo Livshutz", affiliation: "Harry S. Truman College, Chicago, USA" },
      { name: "Mouad Faik", affiliation: "Ensimag and Ecole Polytechnique de Montreal, Canada" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "Hakan Summakoğlu", affiliation: "Antakya, Hatay" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Lim Chang Kiat", affiliation: "Malaysia" },
      { name: "Henry Shin", affiliation: "Harvard University, USA" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "May",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1404q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1405a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Kipp Johnson", affiliation: "Valley Catholic School, Beaverton, Oregon, USA" },
      { name: "Khaled Halaoua", affiliation: "ISSAT, Syria" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Luis Rivera", affiliation: "Universidad Peruana de Ciencias Aplicadas, Lima, Peru" },
      { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology, Korea" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Jan Fricke", affiliation: "University of Siegen, Germany" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Uwe Schafer", affiliation: "Dreieich, Germany" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Lisesi" },
      { name: "Radouan Boukharfane", affiliation: "Polytechnique de Montreal, Canada" },
      { name: "Magnus Jacobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Betül Akbulut", affiliation: "" },
      { name: "Leo Livshutz", affiliation: "Harry S. Truman College, Chicago, USA" },
      { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, UK" },
      { name: "Bazarbay Halmedov", affiliation: "Turgut Özal Turkmen-Turk High School, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "Dovlet Ovlyagulvyev", affiliation: "Turgut Özal Turkmen-Turk High School, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Hakan Summakoğlu", affiliation: "Antakya, Hatay" },
      { name: "Lim Chang Kiat", affiliation: "Malaysia" },
      { name: "Cüneyd Öztürk", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "June",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1405q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1406a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Shatlyk Mamedov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Khaled Halaoua", affiliation: "ISSAT, Syria" },
      { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "July - August",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1406q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1408a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Shatlyk Mamedov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Osman Hacıibrahim", affiliation: "" },
      { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
      { name: "Daniel Salehi", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Michel Bataille", affiliation: "Rouen, France" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Myrat Chashemov", affiliation: "School 21, Dashoguz, Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Lim Chang Kiat", affiliation: "Malaysia" },
      { name: "Paolo Perfetti", affiliation: "Rome, Italy" },
      { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
      { name: "Jishnu Bose", affiliation: "Kolkata, India" },
      { name: "Leo Livshutz", affiliation: "Harry S. Truman College, Chicago, USA" },
      { name: "Cecilia Jarlskog", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "September",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1408q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1409a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Daniel Salehi", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Vanio Beccaccioli", affiliation: "Terni, Italy" },
      { name: "Eskil Jarlskog", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "October",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1409q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1410a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Kipp Johnson", affiliation: "Valley Catholic School, Beaverton, Oregon, USA" },
      { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology, Korea" },
      { name: "Eskil Jarlskog", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
      { name: "Khaled Halaoua", affiliation: "ISSAT, Syria" },
      { name: "Jan van Delden", affiliation: "The Netherlands" },
      { name: "Arthur Vause", affiliation: "Preston, Lancashire, UK" },
      { name: "Hussam Al Daas", affiliation: "UPMC University, Paris, France" },
      { name: "Magnus Jacobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Merdan Soltanov", affiliation: "Turkmenistan" },
      { name: "Leo Livshutz", affiliation: "Harry S. Truman College, Chicago, USA" },
      { name: "Shanur Allabayev", affiliation: "Fatih University" },
      { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Albert Stadler", affiliation: "Herrliberg, Switzerland" },
      { name: "Ananda Raodu", affiliation: "Bangalore, India" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "November",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1410q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1411a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Vedat Deveci", affiliation: "DMO, İstanbul" },
      { name: "Julian Al-Zukaimi", affiliation: "Higher Institue for Applied Science & Technology, Syria" },
      { name: "Mahmut Sait Okyay", affiliation: "Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology, Korea" },
      { name: "Gruian Cornel", affiliation: "Cluj-Napoca, Romania" },
      { name: "Andreas Stiller", affiliation: "c t Computer Magazine, Germany" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Bernard Ivol", affiliation: "Saint-Chamond, France" },
      { name: "Leo Livshutz", affiliation: "Harry S. Truman College, Chicago, USA" },
      { name: "Roger Bengtsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "Hasan Zübeyr Demir", affiliation: "Özel Ankara Çağlayan Lisesi" },
      { name: "Shanur Allabayev", affiliation: "Fatih University" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" }
    ]
  },
  {
    month: "December",
    year: 2014,
    question: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1411q.pdf",
    solution: "https://math.bilkent.edu.tr/Problem/1412a.pdf",
    solvers: [
      { name: "Toshihiro Shimizu", affiliation: "Kawasaki, Japan" },
      { name: "Tomas Jurik", affiliation: "Kosice, Slovakia" },
      { name: "Magnus Jacobsson", affiliation: "Lund, Sweden" },
      { name: "William Wu Cheng Yuan", affiliation: "Singapore" },
      { name: "Leo Livshutz", affiliation: "Harry S. Truman College, Chicago, USA" },
      { name: "Henrik Aberg", affiliation: "Gothenburg, Sweden" },
      { name: "Bojan Basic", affiliation: "Novi Sad, Serbia" },
      { name: "Ananda Raidu", affiliation: "Bangalore, India" },
      { name: "Mehmet Akif Yazıcılar", affiliation: "Bilkent University" }
    ]
  }
];
